

# OMAR **KASHLAN**

COMPUTER ENG & WEB DEV

## **CONTACT**



Syria - Damascus



+963 969 871 572



omaar kashlan 2003@hotmail.com

#### **FOLLOW ME**

facebook/omar.kashlan.5



twitter/omar kashlan



instagram/omar.kashlan



Linkedin/Omar Kashlan

#### **LANGUAGE**

**ARABIC** 

**ENGLISH** 



**FRENCH** 



# **CERTIFICATES**

**HTML** 

UX/UI

**CSS** 

C#

**EXCEL** 

MICROSOFT 365

MORE ON:

https://bit.ly/3NzGQQN



## **AROUT ME**

Hi there, I'm Omar Kashlan.

I have a lot of experience in the field of data entry, web development (front end), video design and editing, and many other experiences related to computers and remote work.

I graduated with very high grades, ranking second in my university, and I look forward to gaining more experience and knowledge.

I am committed to delivering high-quality work and exceeding expectations, and I am excited about the opportunity to bring my skills and experience to a

In general, I am very looking forward to be distinguished in what I do and I will be at the best level I can present.



# **EDUCATION**

### > UNIVERSITY OF THE PEOPLE

NOV 2021- Till Now

Bachelor Degree in Computer Science (4 Years)

#### > DAMASCUS UNIVERSITY

NOV 2021 - AUG 2023

Associate Degree in Computer engineering (2 Years)

#### > ALSAADE SCHOOL

AUG 2020 - SEP 2021

I have been awarded the Certificate of General Secondary Education -Scientific Section — having scored a general average (76.52%).



#### **EXPERIENCE**

# > SALES MANAGER AT VIOLA

FEB 2023 - MARCH 2023

Receiving sales from colleagues at work, entering them into the online system, and entering the appropriate information for the sold item.

#### > CALL CENTER AT MTS

MAY 2022 - JULY 2022

Answer calls and help those who have a problem with the service and provide appropriate solutions to solve their problem.

# > PHARMACIST ASSISTANT

AUG 2021 - OCT 2021

A pharmacist's assistant in a pharmacy in terms of bringing and selling medicines and helping patients.



#### **SKILLS**

ILLUSTRATOR	• • • • •	TEAMWORK	• • • • •
HTML	• • • •	PROBLEM-SOLVING	• • • • •
CSS	$\bullet$ $\bullet$ $\bullet$ $\circ$	LEADERSHIP	• • • • •
JAVA SCRPT	$\bullet$ $\circ$ $\circ$ $\circ$	COMPUTER SKILLS	• • • • •
MS EXCEL	• • • •	GOOGLE DRIVE	• • • • •
VIDEO EDITING	• • • •	WORD PROCESSING	• • • • •
SPREADSHEETS	• • • •	MULTI-TASKING	• • • • •
TYPING SPEED	• • • •	TIME MANAGEMENT	••••